Preliminary guide to the James Goode papers, Circa 1860-2018 MS0670.UA
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Undergraduate and graduate studies, 1964-1995; 1987-1991; Series 1; 4 Linear Feet
  - AMCV 380 U.S. Cultural History, Spring Semester: Literature (Henry Thorean), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - AMCV 380 U.S. Cultural History, Spring Semester: Philosophy (Elizabeth Flower, "A history of philosophy in America"), 1977, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - AMCV 380 U.S. Cultural History, Spring Semester: Reform Movement, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - AMCV 380 U.S. Cultural History, Spring Semester: Religion ("History of Religion in the United States"1960), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - AMCV 380 U.S. Cultural History, Spring Semester: Sectionalism (Frederick Johnson Turner "The significance of section in American History"), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - AMCV 380 U.S. Cultural History, Spring Semester: Slavery, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - AMCV 380 U.S. Cultural History, Spring Semester: Sociology (Robin Williams, "American Society a sociological Intermetabolism"1951), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - AMCV 380 U.S. Cultural History, Spring Semester: Utopias, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - AMCV 380 U.S. Cultural History, Spring Semester: Utopias - Outline, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - AMCV 380 U.S. Cultural History, Spring Semester: A. Jackson (John Ward,), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - AMCV 380 U.S. Cultural History, Spring Semester: Popular Culture (Carl, Bode "The Anatomy of American Popular Culture, 1840-1961), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - German 47. Summer semester: Exercises, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - German 47. Summer semester: Class Notes, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - German 47. Summer semester: Grammar, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - German 47. Summer semester: Vocabulary, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - German 47. Summer semester: Paper, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - German 49. Summer Semester: Class Notes, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - German 49. Summer Semester: Grammar, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - German 49. Summer Semester: Vocabulary, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - German 49. Summer Semester: Exercises, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - German 49. Summer Semester: Essay 1 - Crises, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - German 49. Summer Semester: Essay 2 - Ernest Hemingway, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - German 49. Summer Semester: Essay 3 - The Obligation Remains, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - German 49. Summer Semester: Essay 4 - The Treasure of Montezuma, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - German 49. Summer Semester: Essay 5 - The Entrance of the USA in the War, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - German 49. Summer Semester: Essay 6 - Piazza San Marco, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - German 49. Summer Semester: Essay 7 - Mozat, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - German 49. Summer Semester: Essay 8 - Terrorism, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - German 49. Summer Semester: Essay 9 - Partner in Euro, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - German 49. Summer Semester: Essay 10 - Research & Economy, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - German 49. Summer Semester: Essay 11 - Hemmingway, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - German 49. Summer Semester: Essay 12 - Alberto Giacometti, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - German 49. Summer Semester: Essay 13 - Mozat, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - German 49. Summer Semester: Essay 14 - A New Social Architecture, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - German 49. Summer Semester: Essay 15 - The Future is Launched, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - German 49. Summer Semester: Essay 16 - Ezra Pound, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - German 49. Summer Semester: Essay 17 - Drawings of the Rhine, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - History 398. 18th Century England. Fall Semester: Thomas Hinde, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - History 398. 18th Century England. Fall Semester: Mariam Fowler - "Biography of a Palace", 1990 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - History 398. 18th Century England. Fall Semester: George Rude, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - History 398. 18th Century England. Fall Semester: Adrian Tinniswood, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - History 398. 18th Century England. Fall Semester: Elie Halevy (England in 1815), 1990 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - History 398. 18th Century England. Fall Semester: Donald J. Olsen (Town Planning in London), 1990 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - History 398. 18th Century England. Fall Semester: Dan Cruickshank & Neil Berton (Life in the ______ city), 1990 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - History 398. 18th Century England. Fall Semester: Anthony Dale, James Wyatt, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - History 398. 18th Century England. Fall Semester: Peter Quennell, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - History 398. 18th Century England. Fall Semester: John Summerson (The Life and Work), 1990 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - History 398. 18th Century England. Fall Semester: B. S. Allen, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - History 398. 18th Century England. Fall Semester: Mark Girouard (The Return to Camelot), 1990 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - History 398. 18th Century England. Fall Semester: Richard Reid, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - History 398. 18th Century England. Fall Semester: Christopher Sykes, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - History 398. 18th Century England. Fall Semester: Dorean Yarwood (The architecture of Britain), 1990 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - History 398. 18th Century England. Fall Semester: 18th Century Art, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - History 398. 18th Century England. Fall Semester: Hnmphreys, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - History 398. 18th Century England. Fall Semester: James L. Clifford (Man Venus Society in Eighteenth Century Britain), 1990 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - ARCH History. Extra Readings For Comp Exam For PHD.: Bibliography, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - ARCH History. Extra Readings For Comp Exam For PHD.: Th. Hines, Burnaham of Chicago - Architecture & Planner 1974, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - ARCH History. Extra Readings For Comp Exam For PHD.: H.H. Richardson - (Architectural Forms for an American Society) 1987, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - ARCH History. Extra Readings For Comp Exam For PHD.: McKin & Leland M. Rofth (Harper & Row) 1983, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - ARCH History. Extra Readings For Comp Exam For PHD.: Richard M. Hunt - 1986, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - ARCH History. Extra Readings For Comp Exam For PHD.: Louis Sullivan (His Life & Work, NY) 1986, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - ARCH History. Extra Readings For Comp Exam For PHD.: Albert Kahn (The Architecture of Albert Kahn) MIT- 1974, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - ARCH History. Extra Readings For Comp Exam For PHD.: Richard Neutra (The Search for Wooden Architecture - A biography & history) Oxford - 1982, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - ARCH History. Extra Readings For Comp Exam For PHD.: Chicago Architecture, John Zukowsky (1872-1922, Birth of a Metropolis) Munich - 1987, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - ARCH History. Extra Readings For Comp Exam For PHD.: Auto Tourists - (Americans on the Road) MIT - 1979, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - ARCH History. Extra Readings For Comp Exam For PHD.: Sky Scrapers - (Paul Goldberger, The Sky Scrapers) NY, Alfred A. Knoff - 1981, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - ARCH History. Extra Readings For Comp Exam For PHD.: City Council - (Charles Goodshell, "The city council Chamba") Public Interest, Winter 1984, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - ARCH History. Extra Readings For Comp Exam For PHD.: College Arch. (Helen Horowitz "Designing for the Gardens") Pacific Historical Review. 1985, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - ARCH History. Extra Readings For Comp Exam For PHD.: Roadside Architecture (Chester H. Lide, Main Street & Miracle Mule, American Roadside Architecture) Boston: 1985, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - ARCH History. Extra Readings For Comp Exam For PHD.: Colonial Riverside (The Colonial Riverside in America) New York: 1985, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - ARCH History. Extra Readings For Comp Exam For PHD.: Prairie School (Allen Brooks, The Prairie School,) New York: 1972, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - ARCH History. Extra Readings For Comp Exam For PHD.: Mission Style (David Gebhard, "Architectural Imagery: The mission and California") Spring 1980, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - ARCH History. Extra Readings For Comp Exam For PHD.: Shingle style (Vincent J Scully Jr. The Single Style and the Stitch Style") Yale: 1955, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - ARCH History. Extra Readings For Comp Exam For PHD.: Cranbrook (Robert J. Clark "Design in America" The Cranbrook Vision) New York: 1983, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - ARCH History. Extra Readings For Comp Exam For PHD.: Machine Age (Richard Guy Wilson - "The Machine Age in America") New York: 1986, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - ARCH History. Extra Readings For Comp Exam For PHD.: Art Deco (Richard Sterner - ) 1990, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - ARCH History. Extra Readings For Comp Exam For PHD.: S.F Developers (Anne Brookfield) Munich: 1978, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - ARCH History. Extra Readings For Comp Exam For PHD.: Homes, Work, Class (Lizabeth Cohn - 1885-1915) 1980, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - ARCH History. Extra Readings For Comp Exam For PHD.: Bungalow (Daniel Prosser "Chicago and the Bungalow Boom of the 1920s) Chicago: 1981, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - ARCH History. Extra Readings For Comp Exam For PHD.: Chicago Houses (Wright, "Moralism and the modern home", Domestic Architecture and Cultural Conflict in Chicago 1872-1913) Chicago: 1980, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - ARCH History. Extra Readings For Comp Exam For PHD.: Renaissance (Richard Guy Wilson) 1983, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Arch. History outliners for Comp. Exam PHD: Basic Outline, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Arch. History outliners for Comp. Exam PHD: Colonial, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Arch. History outliners for Comp. Exam PHD: Federal 1785-1820, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Arch. History outliners for Comp. Exam PHD: Greek Revival, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Arch. History outliners for Comp. Exam PHD: Romantic ECL (Homes Gothic Revival), 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Arch. History outliners for Comp. Exam PHD: Modern Architecture, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Arch. History outliners for Comp. Exam PHD: ACAD Electisim (H.H. Richardson, Boston - Modern Architecture), 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Arch. History outliners for Comp. Exam PHD: Highway Architecture, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Arch. History outliners for Comp. Exam PHD: Skyscrapers, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Arch. History outliners for Comp. Exam PHD: House - Virginia 18th Century \, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Arch. History outliners for Comp. Exam PHD: Colonial Revival, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Arch. History outliners for Comp. Exam PHD: City Planning, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Arch. History outliners for Comp. Exam PHD: Technology, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Arch. History outliners for Comp. Exam PHD: Arts & Craft, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Arch. History outliners for Comp. Exam PHD: Commercial Architecture _ office buildings, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Arch. History outliners for Comp. Exam PHD: 3rd Outline - Architectural History, 03/1991 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Resume/CV - James M. Goode, PH.D: G.W. Graduate School (Transcripts), 1987-1995 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Resume/CV - James M. Goode, PH.D: G.W. U.S. Decorative Arts Research Notes for Paper on G.W.'s Entertaining, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Resume/CV - James M. Goode, PH.D: G.W. English Arch. History, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Resume/CV - James M. Goode, PH.D: G.W. U.S Decorative Arts, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Resume/CV - James M. Goode, PH.D: G.W. U.S Urban History, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Resume/CV - James M. Goode, PH.D: G.W. U.S Cultural History, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Resume/CV - James M. Goode, PH.D: G.W. U.S Arch. History, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Course Packet: Material Culture, Course #: A, Cu 253, Professor: Barbara Carson, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: Bibliography, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: Outline, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: Hemphill, Christian D., "Manners for Americans: Interaction, Ritual, and the Social Order, 1620-1860", 1991 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: Smart, Ann Morgan., "The Urban/Rural Dichotomy of Statue Consumption: Tidewater, Virginia, 1815, M.A. - 1986, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: McKendrick - Luxury, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: Cranes, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: Carson & Barbara, Contributions, Appetizers, Dinning and Patterns of Consumption in the United States - 1990, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: Gusfield, Joseph - "Rituals of " - 1988, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: Fox, Elizabeth - (Genovese, Within the Plantation, Black & White Women, The Old South) UNC Press: 1988, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: Goffman, Erveing. "The Presentation of Self in Everyday Life" Woodstock, N.Y.: 1959, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: Bushman, Richard "American High - Style and Vernacular Cultures," Greene & Pole, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: Henretta, James "Wealth and Social Structure", in Greene & Pole, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: Nash, Gary, "Social Development", 1991 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: Sheridan, Richard, "The Domestic Economy" Greene & Pole, Colonial British America, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: Kasson, John "Rudeness & Civility" NY: 1990, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: Peace, W. "Ladies, Women & Wenches, Choices & Constraints in Boston" UNC: 1990, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: Sobel, Mechael, "The World they Made Together, Black and White Values in 18th Century, Virginia" 1987, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: Douglas, Mary, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: Garrett, Elizabeth "The American Home, The Waiting Room" 1984, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: Roth, Rodis, "Tea- Winterberg in 18th Century America" 1988, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: Smith, Billy "the Material Lives of Laborers, 1750 to 1800" 1981, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: Washington Family "Entertaining with the Washington Family: 1789-1799", 1991 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: Class Notes, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: Campbell Consumer: Part 11 - Consumer Revolution, 1700-1850, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: Appleby, Joyce, "Value & Society", 1991 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: Price, Joseph "The Transatlantic Economy", 1991 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: McCraken, Grant "Cultures and Consumers" Bloomington: 1988, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: McKendrick - Consumer 1990, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: Mintz, Sidney W "Sweetness and Power - The Place of Sugar in Modern History" 1985, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: Mukerji, Chandra - 1983, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: Smith, Barbara Clark "After the Revolution" 1985, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: Breene, "Can Empire of Goods" 1986, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 1: McKendrick, Neil "Can 18th Century Europeans in Salesmanship and Marketing Techniques Economic" 1960, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 2: Price, Jacob "Economic Foundation and the Growth of American Port Towns in the 18th Century" 1974, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 2: Robinson, E. "Eighteenth - Century Commerce and Fashion: Matthew Boulton's Marketing Techniques" 1963, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 2: Salinger, Sharon, "________, Journeyman and the Transformation of Labor in the Late 18th Century" 1983, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 2: Walsh, Lorena "Urban Amenities and Rural Sufficiency's: Living Standards and Consumer Behavior in the Colonial Chesapeake, 1643-1777" 1983, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 2: Ceramics, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 2: Wenger, Mark R. "The Dinning Room in Early Virginia" (Part III - Artifacts in the American Household, 1700-1850), 1991 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 2: Garrett, Elizabeth, "The American Family 1750-1870" NY: 1990, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 2: Lemon, James, "Households in Local Communities & Regions", 1991 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 2: Larkin, Jack, "The Reshaping of Everyday Life 1790-1840" NY: 1988, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 2: Wright, Gevendolyn, "Building the Dream, A Social History of Houses in America" NY: 1981, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 2: Ames, Kenneth, "America Decorative Cuts/ Household Furnishings" 1983, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 2: Shammas, Carole "The Domestic Enviornment in Early Modern England and America" 1980, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 3: Artisans - Outline, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 2: Cooper, Wendy "In Praise of America; American Decorative Arts 1950-1830" 1980 - (Part IV - Artifacts and Style, 1700-1850), 1991 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 2: Hardlin, David "The American Home, Architecture and Society, 1815-1915" (Boston: 19779), 1991 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 2: Fitzgerald, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 2: Honour, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 2: Montgomery, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 2: Prowin, Jules "Syle as Evidence" - 1980, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 2: Puig, Frances & Conforti, Michael "The American Craftsmanship and the European Tradition, 1620-1820" 1989, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 2: Goode, James M. Essay: "Dating Four Massachusetts Desks" October, 1988, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 2: Goode, James M. Essay: "The Rebecca Gratz Sideboard, Winterthur Museum" 1988, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 2: Goode, James M. Essay: "A Rococo Teakettle-on-stand by Edward Lownes" 1988, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 2: Class Notes, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 2: Beckow, Stevens M. "Culture, History and Artifact," -(Part V - Historiography), 1991 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 2: Dietz, James "In Small Things Forgotten, The Archeology of Early America", 1991 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 2: Douglass, Mary "The Would of Goods" 1979, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 2: Gowans, Celter "Images of American Living" 1964, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 2: PYE, David "The Six Requirements of Design"1982, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 2: Schelbecker, John "The case of Objects in Historical Research" 1988, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 2: Stocking, George "Objects and Other Essays in Museums and Unilateral Cultures" 1985, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 2: Schlereth, Thomas J. " Material Culture Studies in America, 1876-1976" 1982, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 3: Ames, Kenneth, "Material Culture on Non Verbal Communication: A Historical Case Study" 1980, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 3: Flemming, McClung "Artifact Study a Proposed Model" 1974, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 3: Marchese, Ronald "Material Culture and Artifact Classification" 1980, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 3: Mayo, Edith "Focus on Material Culture" 1980, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 3: Outline: Decorative Cuts, 1700-1850, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 3: Bibliography, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 3: Dinning & Tea Drinking (Social Ritual - Outline), 1991 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 3: Consumer Revolution - Outline, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 3: Households & Furnishings - Outline, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 3: Artifacts - Steps for study and classification - Outline, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 3: History - of Material Culture - Outline, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 3: (Manners) Social Interaction - Outline, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 3: Artisans - Outline, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Decorative Arts, Professor: Carson. Notes, Vol. 3: Blank Paper - Note Outline, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - GW, Urban History Paper on Rowhouses, 1987; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - GW, Urban History, Gillette, 1987; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - GW, Cultural History Readings, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - GW, Decorative Arts, paper on sideboard (part 1), 1988; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - GW, Decorative Arts, paper on sideboard (part 2), 1988; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - GW, Decorative Arts, research for paper on sideboard, 1988; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - GW, Decorative Arts, Teakettle paper, 1988; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - GW, Architectural History, paper on penitentiaries (part I), 1988; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - GW, Architectural History, paper on penitentiaries (part II), 1988; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - GW, Architectural History, paper on penitentiaries (part III), 1988; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - GW, Architectural History 2, Longstreth article, 1988; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - GW, American Airports paper, 1988; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - GW, American Airports paper (part II), 1988; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 5)